briefly.co.za 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

                                          Privacy Policy
Briefly.co.za (“we,” and “us”) respects the privacy of its users and has developed this Privacy
Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the
information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your
choices about such uses and disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully
when using our Service or transacting business with us. By using our Service, you are accepting
the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy
for information on how to contact us.
Information we collect about you
In General. We may collect information that can identify, contact, or locate you such as your name
and email address ("personal information") and other information that does not identify you. When
you provide personal information through our Service, the information may be sent to servers
located in different countries around the world.
        Information you provide. We may collect and store personal information when you register
         and use the Service or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying
         information, such as your name and email address. Information may also be provided by
         corresponding with us (by email or chat, for instance), when you report a problem with the
         Service on our Service, when you subscribe for any of our services, search for a service or
         share data via any of the social media functions on our Service.
        Social Connect. When you choose to connect your social media account to your Service
         profile, we collect Personal Information from that social media website. For example, when
         you connect your Facebook account, we may collect the Personal Information you have
         made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name, user ID, profile picture, cover
         photo, username, gender, networks, age range, language, country, friend list, and any other
         information you have made public. We may also obtain other non-public information from
         social media websites with your permission.
        Geo-location from your device. We may collect and store your location information if your
         device settings are enabled to send it to us. We use this information to analyze user
         behaviour show you personalized content and advertisements.
        Information about others. We may collect and store personal information about other
         people (your friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) that can be obtained when you invite them
         to use our Service, including their name, address and email address.
Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to
collect information from your computer and about your activities on our Service. This helps us to
provide you with a good experience when you use our Service or browse the Website and also
allows us to improve the Service. In particular, we may use Identifier for Advertising (IDFA),
Advertising ID or other similar technologies to track activity of the device you are using for
advertising purposes. The detailed information on how we use cookies and other similar
technologies may be found in the section “Cookies and Other Similar Technologies” below.
        Information collected automatically. We automatically collect information from your browser
         when you visit the Service. This information includes your IP address, your browser type
         and language, information about your device, information about other apps installed on
         your device, access location and times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your
         browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website
         address.
        Cookies and Use of Cookie Data. When you visit our Service, we may assign your device
         one or more cookies to facilitate access to our Service and to personalize your online
         experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information
         about your online activity on the Service, such as the web pages you visit, the time and

       date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our Service. During
       your visits to other websites or online services where we advertise, we (or third parties)
       may use certain data collected on our Service to show you the type of advertisements likely
       to be of greater interest to you. Although you may not opt out of receiving online
       advertisements generally, you may stop targeted Briefly.co.za advertising during your visits
       to other websites and online services. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you
       can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline
       cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive
       features offered on our Service.
      Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and
       other similar technologies, to track your use of our Service. We also may include web
       beacons in advertisements or email messages to determine whether messages have been
       opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize
       the Service we offer our visitors and users to deliver targeted advertisements and to
       measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other
       activities.
      Information collected by third-parties. We may allow third-party partners, including our
       authorized service providers, analytics providers, advertising companies and ad networks,
       to use “cookies” and other similar technologies to collect information about how the Service,
       advertisements, and email are viewed and accessed. We do not provide any personal
       information to these third parties. This information allows us to learn more about how the
       Service is used and for them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their
       effectiveness. Our partners also may collect information about your online activities over
       time, on other devices, and on other websites or online services when they also use our
       partners’ services. When they provide such services, they are governed by their own
       privacy policies.
How we use the information we collect
General. We may use information that we collect about you to:
      enhance your user experience on our Service;
      manage your account and provide you with customer support;
      perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or
       content, or products, Service or content offered by others;
      communicate with you by email, postal mail, push notification, and/or through other digital
       methods about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other
       third parties;
      develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Service and
       other websites and online services;
      detect and resolve any fraud or other illegal or undesirable user behavior;
      perform background checks on users and take other legally-required actions;
      manage our business;
      provide our advertisements to you when you visit other websites and online services;
      perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
Aggregate Data. We may anonymize or aggregate data collected through the Service and use and
disclose it for any purpose.
With whom we share your information
Personal information. We share your personal information with others as indicated below or when
we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared.
We may share personal information with:
      Service providers. We may share your personal information, which may include your name
       and contact information (including email address) with third parties that perform certain

        service on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer
        service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, member
        screenings, supporting our Service functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes,
        surveys and other features offered through our Service.
       Other Users. We will share your profile information with other users of the Service. We will
        also facilitate sending the messages between you and other users, and so your message
        content will be shared with the recipient.
       Marketing. We may allow access to data collected by the Service and our service providers
        to enable the delivery of online advertising on the Service or on other websites and online
        services, or to send you information we think may be useful or relevant to you. We may
        also provide your contact information to others for their marketing purposes.
       Business partners. When you register on our Service or click-through our advertisements
        offered on third party websites and online services, we may share personal information with
        the businesses with which we partner to offer you the applicable products, services or any
        advertisements. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you
        authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant. In
        addition, when you click on an advertisement on our Service relating to a particular
        merchant, you authorize us to provide your personal information (such as your photograph,
        age and gender) to that merchant for the purposes of facilitating the completion of your
        registration with that merchant's web-site or service and for other purposes in accordance
        with the privacy policy and terms of use of that merchant (please refer to the "Third-Party
        Websites" section below for additional information).
       Other Situations. We also may disclose your information, including personal information:
    -   In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for
        cooperation from law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our
        legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases,
        we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
    -   When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent,
        or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to
        protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees,
        or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce
        our Service terms or other agreements or policies.
    -   In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a
        divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
Aggregated and/or non-personal information. We may share non-personal information we collect
under any of the above circumstances. We may combine non-personal information we collect with
additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated,
non-personal information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, with third
parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general
business analysis or other business purposes.
Personalized Advertising. You may be able to opt out of receiving personalized advertisements
from advertisers or advertising networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or
who subscribe to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral
Advertising by visiting the opt-out sections on the websites of each of those organizations. Links to
those sites are here:
       Network Advertising Initiative: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
       Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
You may opt out of personalized ads from AdCash at https://www.adcash.com/legal-
info/#h.ew5sib19a7w8

When you opt out of personalized advertising, you may continue to see online advertising on the
Service and/or our ads on other Internet websites and online services.
How to unsubscribe from future email marketing messages
You may unsubscribe from marketing emails by using the unsubscribe link in a marketing email.
Please note that even after you opt-out of marketing messages, we may still communicate with you
by email for administrative and informational purposes unrelated to marketing. The subscribers of
our Service’s app may also unsubscribe from all notifications by following the appropriate steps in
the “Manage notifications” section of the settings.
Third-party websites
There are a number of places on our Service where you may click on a link to access other
websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an
advertisement on our Service, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-
party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information,
from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those
websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you
visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.
How you can access your information
If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to us through your use
of the Service, you may use the Service to do so. If you need help, or if you have suggestions for
improving this Privacy Policy, please send an email to privacy@gen.tech.
If you have an online account with us, you may close it via request to Support. After you close your
account, you will not be able to sign in to our Service or access any of your personal information.
However, you can open a new, separate account at any time or re-activate your previous account
by following instructions we will give you at the time you close your account. If you close your
account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical
purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, take
actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Service or our users, or take other
actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to
third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those
third parties' policies.
Your choices about collection and use of your information
        You can control information collected by cookies. See section "Cookies" below for
         information about declining or deleting cookies.
How we protect your personal information
We take reasonable security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to
help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We want you
to feel confident using our Service to transact business. However, no system can be completely
secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you
should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always
remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal
information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email.
Information you provide about yourself while using our Service
We provide areas on our Service where you can post information about yourself and others and
communicate with others. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when
searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose

personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and
can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive
unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with
the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with
respect to your personal information.
Children's privacy
Although our Service is a general audience service, we restrict the use of our Service to individuals
age 18 and above. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from
children under 18 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed to children under the age of
18. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, you
may alert us at privacy@gen.tech. If we learn that we have collected any personal information from
children under 18, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s
account.
International Data Transfers
Briefly.co.za is a global business. We may transfer personal information to countries other than the
country in which the data was originally collected. These countries may not have the same data
protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer
your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this
Privacy Policy.
In particular, to offer our Service, we need to transfer your personal information to the United
States. The United States is not considered to provide an adequate level of protection under EU
data protection law. By agreeing to the Privacy Policy, you consent to the transfer of your personal
information for the purposes described in the Privacy Policy. You have the right to withdraw your
consent at any time, but please note that if you do not consent to the transfer of if you withdraw
your consent to transfer, you may not be able to benefit from all or some of our services.
If you would like to withdraw your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to the U.S.,
please send us an email to privacy@gen.tech.
No Rights of Third Parties
This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any
personal information relating to users of the website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Service from
time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies. If
our practices change regarding previously collected Personal Information in a way that would be
materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we
collected the information, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to
any such uses as may be required by law.
California Privacy Rights
Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in
obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and
obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any,
with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses.
To obtain this information from us, please send an email message to privacy@gen.tech or mail us
at the address below with “Request for California Privacy Information” on the subject line and in the
body of your message. If you are a California resident, we will provide the requested information to
you at your e-mail address in response.

Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements
and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.
Cookies and Other Similar Technologies
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes.
Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you
close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our Service. A persistent
cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Cookies on our Service do not
link to or store your personal information.
For example, when you sign in to our Service, we will record your user ID and the name associated
with your user ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this
cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For
security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-
related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user
or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service
providers to serve cookies from our Service to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as
doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our Service, content and advertising.
You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar
of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our Service
may not function properly.
We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on
our Service. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect
information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our Service does not
provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about
where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they
deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements
clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to
the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they
collect from you to provide advertisements about goods and Service likely to be of greater interest
to you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This
information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.
Web Beacons
Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique
identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users
or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web
beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the
period at the end of this sentence..
Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have
visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous
identification number if you come to our Service from an online advertisement displayed on a third-
party website. Third parties may use anonymous information about your visits to our Service and
other websites in order to improve its products and Service and provide advertisements about
goods and Service of interest to you.
Last Updated: 16.05.2018
